# **ADI BADER**

## Givat-Haim, Israel



## Front End Developer / PM

✓ adibader1@gmail.com

Github

After 6 years of experience in the CMS industry. With a high level of experience with HTML and CSS, as well as a deep knowledge of the UX/UI principles, and strong design skills. I recently expanded my front-end tool box, by acquiring a firm knowledge and experience with JavaScript and React JS.

I am now looking for my next challenge, a long-term job, in which I can express my wide range of abilities. I am eager to develop my professional skills as well as acquiring new proficiencies. I am open for both front-end and product management positions.

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

### 2017-2022: Interdeal development

Head of community centers department • Build and designed websites with CMS platforms • Managed projects • Coordinated between costumer needs and the company's technical solutions • Used HTML, CSS • Used JavaScript • Implemented jQuery codes • Committed responsive adjustments to websites • Managed e-commerce websites • Used high design skills • Gave excellent technical support and guidance to customers.

#### 2016: Weizmann Institute of Science

Build and designed websites • Gave consulting services to scientists in the field of building and designing websites • Used HTML / CSS • Implemented jQuery codes • Worked with Drupal platform.

## 2014-2016: Owner of a branding and websites building business

Build and designed websites • Managed websites content • Created graphic materials for businesses • Build branding for businesses.

\*Serves as a medic on army reserve.

#### **EDUCATION**

#### 2022: React JS course - React Front to Back 2022

studied the foundations of React JS and build a variety of web applications.

#### 2022: JavaScript course - The Complete JavaScript Course 2022

studied the foundations of JavaScript and build a variety of web applications.

#### 2013-2015: Interactive Media studies - Ruppin Technological College.

As part of the studies, I participated in courses such as:

Interactive Media Design, UX/UI Design, Fundamentals of Graphic Design, Fundamentals of Marketing, Integrated Marketing, Websites Building and FLASH.

#### **PERSONAL QUALITIES**

Highly motivated team player with great interpersonal skills. Highly ambitious to study and improve. Owns a high work ethic, with a high level of customer service orientation and strong management abilities. Highly creative and an autodidact.

#### **SKILLS:**

JavaScript, React JS, HTML, CSS, TypeScript, Angular, UX/UI, design, project managing, costumer support.